datahat.com.au 2017-09-13

# Privacy Policy – Data Hat

**Who are we?**

Datahat is a digital marketing business that works with leading publishers to manage and monetize their data and audiences. We respect the privacy of all those who use the services we provide. We have a simple policy that we will not willfully disclose any personal information regarding our users without first obtaining their permission, unless required by law. By using our web sites, you consent to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this policy and to our Terms and Conditions of Use.

**Use of Cookies**

A “cookie” is a file sent to your browser by a Web server and stored on your computer, it contains data that Web sites use to identify you as a unique user. Companies which advertise on our site may collect information from you if you click on their advertisements or access their sites. They may do this by using cookies. Due to the way the Internet operates, we cannot control this collection of information. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can change the settings of your browser to refuse all cookies or to notify you each time a cookie is sent to your computer, giving you the choice whether to accept it or not.

If you have any questions or concerns about the way in which information is collected or used by another site, then you should contact whoever is responsible for that site directly.

**What Information do we Collect?**

We do not collect any personal information about you (such as your name or email address) except when you specifically and knowingly provide that information. We do keep a record of the IP addresses from which users access our site. This data is used by us for internal administration, and to analyze the way in which people use our site, so that we can keep improving the services we offer. This data also provides us with anonymous and broad demographic information about those using our site.

**Do we disclose information to anyone else?**

We do not disclose any information about our site users to any 3rd party. For example, we may disclose the total number of “hits” our sites receive, or how often the average user visits our site, or which terms are most often entered in our search engine. Please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required by law. We receive and reply to email from users on a regular basis. For record-keeping purposes, we retain copies of all incoming and outgoing email. Information in the email we receive or send will not be disclosed to any third party without the permission of the sender, either express or implied, unless required by law.

**Links**

Our websites and databases contain a large number of links to external sites. Please be aware that these external sites are developed by people over whom we have no control, and we are not responsible for their privacy practices. This Privacy Policy applies only to all websites that Datahat owns or represents. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy policy of any Web site you visit which collects personal information, and to exercise discretion when providing such information.

**Cookies**

To help you understand how we use cookies we refer to cookie we place on owned and operated sites, (we refer as ‘first party cookies’) and those placed by third party domains (we refer to as ‘third party cookies’). Whether a cookie is a ‘first’ or ‘third’ party refers to whether the domain that places the cookie into your browser is the same domain as the page you are visiting at the time the cookie is placed. If a user visits a website and a separate domain sets a cookie through that website, it is referred to as a third party cookie. Note in some cases our cookies may be served as ‘third party’ cookies on the domain of another company in our Publisher Network.

We will update this list periodically as we make changes to cookies used as part of the experience across websites, mobile websites and mobile applications; or if we can provide more specific information in relation to the cookies used on our platform. Note web, mobile, tablet and apps may not always use the same cookies.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time at our discretion and without notice. If we do, an updated version of this Privacy Policy will be made available on this site so that you remain aware of the data we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Further information**

Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions, comments or would like more information. You can contact the team here. This Privacy Statement is version 2.1, and replaces all previous versions.
